[
    {
        "question": "Акмурат Ходжатов",
        "answer": "Akmurat Khodzhatov",
        "variants": [
            "Akmurat Khodzhatov",
            "Akmurat Khojatov",
            "Akmurat Hodzhatov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Ходыкин",
        "answer": "Aleksandr Khodykin",
        "variants": [
            "Aleksandr Khodykin",
            "Alexander Khodykin",
            "Aleksandr Hodykin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Поляков",
        "answer": "Alexander Polyakov",
        "variants": [
            "Alexander Polyakov",
            "Aleksandr Polyakov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Жидовленко",
        "answer": "Alexander Zhidovlenko",
        "variants": [
            "Alexander Zhidovlenko",
            "Aleksandr Zhidovlenko"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Зуев",
        "answer": "Alexander Zuev",
        "variants": [
            "Alexander Zuev",
            "Aleksandr Zuev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Артюхов",
        "answer": "Alexandr Artyukhov",
        "variants": [
            "Alexandr Artyukhov",
            "Alexander Artyukhov",
            "Aleksandr Artyuhov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Леонов",
        "answer": "Alexandr Leonov",
        "variants": [
            "Alexandr Leonov",
            "Alexander Leonov",
            "Aleksandr Leonov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Александр Вежлев",
        "answer": "Alexandr Vezhlev",
        "variants": [
            "Alexandr Vezhlev",
            "Alexander Vezhlev",
            "Aleksandr Vezhlev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Амаль Абдуллаев",
        "answer": "Amal Abdullaev",
        "variants": [
            "Amal Abdullaev",
            "Akmal Abdullayev",
            "Amal Abdullayev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Антон Машошин",
        "answer": "Anton Mashoshin",
        "variants": [
            "Anton Mashoshin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Дарья Голубева",
        "answer": "Darya Golubeva",
        "variants": [
            "Darya Golubeva",
            "Daria Golubeva"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Денис Хрипков",
        "answer": "Denis Khripkov",
        "variants": [
            "Denis Khripkov",
            "Denis Hripkov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Дима Нгуен",
        "answer": "Dmitriy Nguyen",
        "variants": [
            "Dmitriy Nguyen",
            "Dima Nguyen",
            "Dima Nguen"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Дмитрий Данилов",
        "answer": "Dmitry Danilov",
        "variants": [
            "Dmitry Danilov",
            "Dmitrij Danilov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Дмитрий Гадеев",
        "answer": "Dmitry Gadeev",
        "variants": [
            "Dmitry Gadeev",
            "Dmitriy Gadeev",
            "Dmitrij Gadeev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Егор Ней",
        "answer": "Egor Ney",
        "variants": [
            "Egor Ney",
            "Yegor Ney",
            "Egor Nej"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Егор Половинкин",
        "answer": "Egor Polovinkin",
        "variants": [
            "Egor Polovinkin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Игорь Буруля",
        "answer": "Igor Burulya",
        "variants": [
            "Igor Burulya",
            "Igor Burbulya"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Игорь Дизгинжили",
        "answer": "Igor Dizginzhili",
        "variants": [
            "Igor Dizginzhili"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Иван Брякунов",
        "answer": "Ivan Bryakunov",
        "variants": [
            "Ivan Bryakunov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Кирилл Столяров",
        "answer": "Kirill Stolyarov",
        "variants": [
            "Kirill Stolyarov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Константин Грушин",
        "answer": "Konstantin Grushin",
        "variants": [
            "Konstantin Grushin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Максим Алехнович",
        "answer": "Maksim Alekhnovich",
        "variants": [
            "Maksim Alekhnovich",
            "Maxim Alekhnovich",
            "Maksim Alehnovich"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Максим Чернухин",
        "answer": "Maksim Chernukhin",
        "variants": [
            "Maksim Chernukhin",
            "Maxim Chernukhin",
            "Maksim Chernuhin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Марина Алексюк",
        "answer": "Marina Aleksyuk",
        "variants": [
            "Marina Aleksyuk",
            "Marina Alexiuk"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Михаил Авдеев",
        "answer": "Mikhail Avdeev",
        "variants": [
            "Mikhail Avdeev",
            "Mihail Avdeev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Михаил Сороколет",
        "answer": "Mikhail Sorokolet",
        "variants": [
            "Mikhail Sorokolet",
            "Mikhail Sorokoletov",
            "Mihail Sorokolet"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Наталия Шпер",
        "answer": "Natalia Shper",
        "variants": [
            "Natalia Shper",
            "Nataliya Shper"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Николай Лаевский",
        "answer": "Nikolai Laevskii",
        "variants": [
            "Nikolai Laevskii",
            "Nikolai Laevsky",
            "Nikolay Laevsky",
            "Nikolaj Laevskij"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Николай Шубин",
        "answer": "Nikolay Shubin",
        "variants": [
            "Nikolay Shubin",
            "Nikolai Shubin",
            "Nikolaj Shubin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Никита Нафранец",
        "answer": "Nikita Nafranets",
        "variants": [
            "Nikita Nafranets",
            "Nikita Nafranec"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Олег Кузняк",
        "answer": "Oleg Kuznyak",
        "variants": [
            "Oleg Kuznyak",
            "Oleg Kuzniak"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Олег Морозов",
        "answer": "Oleg Morozov",
        "variants": [
            "Oleg Morozov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ольга Копьева",
        "answer": "Olga Kopyeva",
        "variants": [
            "Olga Kopyeva",
            "Olga Kopjeva",
            "Olga Kopeva"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Павел Андреев",
        "answer": "Pavel Andreev",
        "variants": [
            "Pavel Andreev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Паша Старовойтов",
        "answer": "Pavel Starovoytov",
        "variants": [
            "Pavel Starovoytov",
            "Pasha Starovoitov",
            "Pasha Starovojtov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Роман Гранков",
        "answer": "Roman Grankov",
        "variants": [
            "Roman Grankov",
            "Roman Croutons"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Роман Новожилов",
        "answer": "Roman Novozhilov",
        "variants": [
            "Roman Novozhilov"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Сергей Пеняев",
        "answer": "Penyaev Sergey",
        "variants": [
            "Penyaev Sergey",
            "Sergey Penyaev",
            "Sergei Penyaev",
            "Sergej Penyaev"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Сергей Сахаровский",
        "answer": "Sergei Sakharovskii",
        "variants": [
            "Sergei Sakharovskii",
            "Sergey Sakharovsky",
            "Sergei Sakharovsky",
            "Sergej Saharovskij"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Степан Быстрай",
        "answer": "Stepan Bystray",
        "variants": [
            "Stepan Bystray",
            "Stepan Bystry",
            "Stepan Bystraj"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Владислав Перетягин",
        "answer": "Vlad Peretyagin",
        "variants": [
            "Vlad Peretyagin",
            "Vladislav Peretyagin"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Всеволод Андрущенко",
        "answer": "Vsevolod Andruschenko",
        "variants": [
            "Vsevolod Andruschenko",
            "Vsevolod Andryushchenko",
            "Vsevolod Andrushchenko",
            "Vsevolod Andrushenko"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ян Павленко",
        "answer": "Yann Pavlenko",
        "variants": [
            "Yann Pavlenko",
            "Jan Pavlenko",
            "Yan Pavlenko"
        ]
    },
    {
        "question": "Ян Парфенов",
        "answer": "Yan Parfenov",
        "variants": [
            "Yan Parfenov",
            "Jan Parfenov"
        ]
    }
]